{
	"questions_and_answers": [
		{
			"question": "What is the campus address of NMAM Institute of Technology?",
			"answer": "The campus address of NMAM Institute of Technology is: Nitte, Karkala Taluk, Udupi - 574110, Karnataka, India. For further details refer: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/contact-nmamit.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "What are the contact phone numbers for NMAM Institute of Technology?",
			"answer": "The contact phone numbers for NMAM Institute of Technology are: +91 - 8258 - 281263 / 281264 / 281248 / 281461 / 281462 / 281463 / 281349, and +91 - 8258 - 281039. For further details refer: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/contact-nmamit.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the email address of the Director (CM & D) at NMAM Institute of Technology?",
			"answer": "The email address of the Director (CM & D) at NMAM Institute of Technology is reg_nitte@nitte.edu.in. For further details refer: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/contact-nmamit.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the email address of the Chief Warden at NMAM Institute of Technology?",
			"answer": "The email address of the Chief Warden at NMAM Institute of Technology is chiefwarden@nmamit.in. For further details refer: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/contact-nmamit.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the email address of the Exam office at NMAM Institute of Technology?",
			"answer": "The email address of the Exam office at NMAM Institute of Technology is coe.nmamit@nitte.edu.in. For further details refer: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/contact-nmamit.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the email address of the Deputy Registrar (NDU) at NMAM Institute of Technology?",
			"answer": "The email address of the Deputy Registrar (NDU) at NMAM Institute of Technology is dreg@nitte.edu.in. For further details refer: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/contact-nmamit.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the email address of the Public Relations Officer at NMAM Institute of Technology?",
			"answer": "The email address of the Public Relations Officer at NMAM Institute of Technology is krishnaraja@nitte.edu.in. For further details refer: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/contact-nmamit.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the email address of the Student Welfare Officer at NMAM Institute of Technology?",
			"answer": "The email address of the Student Welfare Officer at NMAM Institute of Technology is shashikanth@nitte.edu.in. For further details refer: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/contact-nmamit.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "Who is the placement head of NMAM Institute of Technology?",
			"answer": "Mr. Bharath G. Kumar is the placement head of NMAM Institute of Technology"
		},
		{
			"question": "what is the email of placement department Nitte?",
			"answer": "the email of placement department is placement.nmamit@nitte.edu.in"
		},
		{
			"question": "what is the phone number of placement department Nitte?",
			"answer": "the phone number of placement department is +91 9902414602"
		},
		{
			"question": "who is the Counsellor of Abhyuday?",
			"answer": "Mr. Ankith S Kumar is th counsellor of abhyuday"
		}
	]
}
